JULY 16TH (FRI) 7:57 AM
FLIP
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
Let the joy of love
give you an answer
Our Willis unbreakable
even when it's time to part
1999 Bizarre Summer
This is the hymn born from
our fearless hearts
Great Days
Breakdown, Breakdown
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
July 16th (Fri) 8:27 AM
EPISODE 36
BITES THE DUST, PART 2
IT RAINED.
AT 8:27 AM, LIGHTNING STRUCK
ABOVE THE PEPSI SIGN.
HAYATO KAWAJIRI
WAKE UP
WEATHER REPORT BEGINS
KIRA LEAVES HOUSE
HAYATO MEETS ROHAN
LIGHTNING STRIKES PEPSI SIGN
EXPLOSION KILLS ROHAN KISHIBE
JULY 16TH (FRI) 8:34 AM
EPISODE 37
SHINING D (DIAMOND)
IS UNBREAKABLE, PART 1